(Sheldon:)Crafty old gal.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, but you are not the
only distinguished scientist
(Leonard:)in this apartment.
(Leonard:)I've been published in
peer-reviewed journals,
(Leonard:)I received a Dissertation
of the Year award
(Leonard:)for experimental
particle physics.
(Sheldon:)No, that can't be it.
(Sheldon:)And since you seem
(Sheldon:)to have forgotten,
the reason we live together
(Sheldon:)is we're best friends.
(Sheldon:)And I got your back, Jack.
(Leonard:)That was a great meal.
I'm glad you
enjoyed it.
(Leonard:)The only time I eat this well
is when my mom's in town
(Leonard:)- and she takes me out to dinner.
- Is that so?
(Leonard:)You kind of
remind me of her.
(Leonard:)She enjoys making people
uncomfortable, too.
(Mrs Latham:)Well, you remind me of
a boy I dated in college.
- No kidding.
- Sweet boy.
(Mrs Latham:)Very smart.
(Mrs Latham:)If only he'd had money.
(Leonard:)Yeah, um...
(Leonard:)so, hey,
speaking of money,
(Leonard:)how are you feeling about
helping the physics department
(Leonard:)get a cryogenic centrifugal
pump and molecular sieve?